Merry Christmas, Drake & Josh is a comedy, family, tv
movie film directed by Michael Grossman.
Step brothers Drake and Josh must give a foster family the best Christmas
ever or face years in jail for a Christmas party gone wrong.
Drake Parker, played by Drake Bell.
Josh Nichols, played by Josh Peck.
Megan Parker, played by Miranda Cosgrove.
Mary Alice Johansson, played by Bailee Madison.
Audrey Parker-Nichols, played by Nancy Sullivan.
Walter Nichols, played by Jonathan Goldstein.
Merry Christmas, Drake & Josh (also known as Drake & Josh: Best Christmas Ever) is a 2008
American Christmas comedy television film based on the Nickelodeon sitcom Drake & Josh.
Drake Bell, Josh Peck, Miranda Cosgrove, Nancy Sullivan, and Jonathan Goldstein reappear as their
respective characters, with several recurring characters from the TV series also reappearing.
The film premiered on December 5, 2008 as a Nickelodeon Original
Movie, a year after the show's original end in 2007.
As such, it also serves as the narrative conclusion of Drake & Josh.
It was the third most viewed TV movie on cable behind High School Musical 2 and
Wizards of Waverly Place: The Movie, both owned by Disney Channel.
The tone is lighthearted.